lonerwolf.com 2019-07-11

# Privacy Policy ⋆ LonerWolf

## Privacy Policy for LonerWolf.Com

The privacy of our visitors to LonerWolf is important to us.

At LonerWolf, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit LonerWolf, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### The Information We Collect on this website.

We collect different types of information from or through this website. The legal bases for LonerWolf’s processing of personal data are primarily that the processing is necessary for providing this Site in accordance with LonerWolf’s [Terms of Service](https://lonerwolf.com/terms-and-conditions/) and that the processing is carried out in LonerWolf’s legitimate interests, which are further explained in the section “How We Use the Information We Collect” of this Policy. We may also process data upon your consent, asking for it as appropriate.

#### **User-provided Information**

When you use our website, as a User, Customer or as a Visitor, you may provide, and we may collect Personal Data. Examples of Personal Data include name, email address, mailing address, mobile phone number, and credit card or other billing information. Personal Data also includes other information, such as geographic area or preferences, when any such information is linked to information that identifies a specific individual. You may provide us with Personal Data in various ways on the Site. For example, when you register for an Account, purchase a Product from our shop, post a comment, interact with other users of the Site through communication or messaging capabilities, or send us customer service -related requests.

##### Commenting

We collect information about visitors who comment on the site using the Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available [here](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### **Automatically Collected Information**

When a User or Visitor uses our website, we may automatically record certain information from the User’s or Visitor’s device by using various types of technology, including cookies, “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This “automatically collected” information may include IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites visited, the pages or other content the User or Visitor views or interacts with, and the dates and times of the visit, access, or use of the website. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding a Visitor or User’s interaction with email messages, such as whether the Visitor or User opens, clicks on, or forwards a message. This information is gathered from all Users and Visitors.

#### **Integrated Services**

You may be given the option to access or register to the website through the use of your user name and passwords for certain services provided by third parties (each, an “Integrated Service”), such as through the use of your Google/Facebook account, or otherwise have the option to authorize an Integrated Service to provide Personal Data or other information to us (such as Mailchimp.com, which we use for our Email Newsletter/Communication). By authorizing us to connect with an Integrated Service, you authorize us to access and store your name, email address(es), date of birth, gender, current city, profile picture URL, and other information that the Integrated Service makes available to us, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Policy. You should check your privacy settings on each Integrated Service to understand what information that Integrated Service makes available to us, and make changes as appropriate. Please review each Integrated Service’s terms of use and privacy policies carefully before using their services and connecting to our Site.

### How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information that we collect in a variety of ways in providing the Site and operating our business, including the following:

#### Operations

We use the information to operate, maintain, enhance and provide all features of the website, to provide the services and information that you request, to respond to comments and questions and to provide support to users of the website. We process data solely in accordance with the directions provided by the applicable Customer or User.

### eCommerce

Another way we use this information includes processing the transactions of our eCommerce store by collecting the data you submit during the checkout procedure and securely passing on to our Payment Processing Service (Stripe or Paypal).

##### eCommerce – What we collect and store

While you visit our site, we’ll track:

  * Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewed
  * Location, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shipping
  * Shipping address: we’ll ask you to enter this so we can, for instance, estimate shipping before you place an order, and send you the order!
  * We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.

When you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We’ll use this information for purposes, such as, to:

  * Send you information about your account and order.
  * Respond to your requests, including refunds and complaints.
  * Process payments and prevent fraud.
  * Set up your account for our store.
  * Comply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxes.
  * Improve our store offerings.
  * Send you marketing messages, if you choose to receive them.
  * If you create an account, we will store your name, address, email and phone number, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.

We generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. For example, we will store order information for 7 years for tax and accounting purposes. This includes your name, email address and billing and shipping addresses.

We will also store comments or reviews, if you choose to leave them.

##### eCommerce – Who on our team has access  
Members of our team have access to the information you provide us. For example, both Administrators and Shop Managers can access: 

  * Order information like what was purchased, when it was purchased and where it should be sent, and
  * Customer information like your name, email address, and billing and shipping information.
  * Our team members have access to this information to help fulfill orders, process refunds and support you.

##### eCommerce – What we share with others

In this section you should list who you’re sharing data with, and for what purpose. This could include, but may not be limited to, analytics, marketing, payment gateways, shipping providers, and third party embeds.

We share information with third parties who help us provide our orders and store services to you; for example —

##### eCommerce – Payments

We accept payments through Stripe and PayPal. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to Stripe/PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information.

Please see the [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) and [Stripes](https://stripe.com/gb/privacy) Private Policies for more details.

#### Improvements

We use the information to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our Visitors and Users, to improve the website, and to develop new products, services, feature, and functionality. Should this purpose require LonerWolf to process data, then the data will only be used in anonymized or aggregated form.

#### Communications

We may use a Visitor’s or User’s email address or other information to contact that Visitor or User for administrative purposes such as customer service or product support.

#### Cookies and Tracking Technologies

We use automatically collected information and other information collected on the website through cookies and similar technologies to: ( **i** ) personalize our website, such as remembering a User’s or Visitor’s information and preferences so that the User or Visitor will not have to re-enter it during a visit or on subsequent visits (e.g: Closing a popup window will disable it from appearing for 30 days, saving your name/email when leaving a comment for 365 days); ( **ii** ) provide customized advertisements, content, and information; ( **iii** ) monitor and analyze the effectiveness of our website and third-party marketing activities; ( **iv** ) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and ( **v** ) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities on the website. You can obtain more information about cookies by visiting [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### Embedded Content From Other Websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on the Public Area of the website, and create user navigation reports for our Site administrators. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which we strongly suggest you review. Google may use the information collected through Google Analytics to evaluate Users and Visitors activity on our site. For more information, see [Google Analytics Privacy and Data Sharing](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245) and the [documentation](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) of the cookies they use.

We take measures to protect the technical information collected by our use of Google Analytics. The data collected is all anonymized and will only be used on a need to know basis to resolve technical issues, administer the website and identify visitor preferences; but in this case, the data will be in non-identifiable form. We do not use any of this information to identify Visitors or Users.

You may opt out from the collection of navigation information about your visit to this website by using our Google Analytics “Opt-Out” link. Click here to Opt-Out of LonerWolf tracking you via Google Analytics.

### Your Choices

#### Access, Correction, Deletion

We respect your privacy rights and provide you with reasonable access to the Personal Data that you may have provided through your use of this website. If you wish to access or amend any other Personal Data we hold about you, or to request that we delete or transfer any information about you that we have obtained from an Integrated Service, you may contact us as set forth in the “How to Contact Us” section. At your request, we will have any reference to you deleted or blocked in our database.

You may update, correct, or delete your Account information and preferences at any time by accessing your Account settings page on our website. Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so.

You may decline to share certain Personal Data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality of this website.

### Interest Based Advertising

Interest based advertising is the collection of data from different sources and across different platforms in order to predict an individual’s preferences or interest and to deliver to that individual, or his/her computer, smart phone or tablet, advertising based on his/her assumed preference or interest inferred from the collection of data pertaining to that individual or others who may have a similar profile or similar interests.

We work with a variety of third parties to attempt to understand the profiles of the individuals who are most likely to be interested in the LonerWolf products or services so that we can send them promotional emails, or serve our advertisements to them on the websites and mobile apps of other entities.

These third parties include: (a) advertising networks, which collect information about a person’s interests when that person views or interacts with one of their advertisements; (2) attribution partners, which measure the effectiveness of certain advertisements; and (3) business partners, which collect information when a person views or interacts with one of their advertisements.

In collaboration with these third parties, we collect information about our customers, prospects and other individuals over time and across different platforms when they use these platforms or interact with them. Individuals may submit information directly on this website or on platforms run by third parties, or by interacting with us, our advertisements, or emails they receive from us or from third parties. We may use special tools that are commonly used for this purpose, such as cookies, beacons, pixels, tags, mobile advertising IDs, flash cookies, and similar technologies. We may have access to databases of information collected by our business partners.

The information we or third party collect enables us to learn what purchases the person made, what ads or content the person sees, on which ads or links the person clicks, and other actions that the person takes on our Sites, or in response to our emails, or when visiting or using third parties’ platforms.

We, or the third parties with which we work, use the information collected as described above to understand the various activities and behaviors of our customers, Site visitors and others. We, or these third parties, do this for many reasons, including: to recognize new or past visitors to our website; to present more personalized content; to provide more useful and relevant ads – for example, if we know what ads you are shown we can try not to show you the same ones repeatedly; to identify visitors across devices, sales channels, third party websites and Sites, or to display or send personalized or targeted ads and other custom content that is more focused on a person’s perceived interest in products or services similar to those that we offer.

Our interest-based ads may be served to you in emails or on third-party platforms. We may serve these ads about our products or services or send commercial communications directly ourselves or through these third parties.

Visitors may opt out of receiving interest based advertising by advertising networks that may be delivered to them on our platform and other websites by visiting the following websites: http://www.aboutads.info/consumers; and http://www.networkadvertising.org. These features will opt a Visitor out of many – but not all – of the interest-based advertising activities in which we or third parties engage.

Other third-party Sites provide visitors with the ability to opt-out of receiving interest-based ads on their Sites that you need to control through your settings on that Site. For example, to opt out of Google’s use of your online behavior for advertising purposes, visit Google’s Ad Settings page.

#### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”).

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Indian, you may see New Delhi hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about traveling). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

### Third-Party Services

LonerWolf.com may contain features or links to web sites and services provided by third parties. Any information you provide on third-party sites or services is provided directly to the operators of such services and is subject to those operators’ policies, if any, governing privacy and security. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through this website. We encourage you to learn about third parties’ privacy and security policies before providing them with information.

### Data Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect Personal Data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Data in our possession. This includes, for example, firewalls, password protection and other access and authentication controls. We use SSL technology to encrypt data during transmission through public internet, and we also employ application-layer security features to further anonymize Personal Data.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or store on the Site, and you do so at your own risk. We also cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If you believe your Personal Data has been compromised, please contact us as set forth in the “How to Contact Us” section.

If we learn of a security systems breach, we will inform you and the authorities of the occurrence of the breach in accordance with applicable law.

### Data Retention

We only retain the Personal Data collected from a User for as long as the User’s account is active or otherwise for a limited period of time as long as we need it to fulfill the purposes for which we have initially collected it, unless otherwise required by law. We will retain and use information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements as follows:

  * Google Analytics user collected data is retained indefinitely unless deletion is requested by the Visitor or Customer.
  * Customers Name and Email Address are collected indefinitely in order for us to be able to store and deliver their digital purchases upon request of a new receipt or download links. We will delete this data upon request of the customer.

### Changes and Updates to this Policy

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Policy, which we may update from time to time. If we modify the Policy, we will make it available through the website navigation, and indicate the date of the latest revision, and will comply with applicable law. Your continued use of the Site after the revised Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of the Policy.

### How to Contact Us

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Policy, your Personal Data, our use and disclosure practices, or your consent choices by email using our [contact form](https://lonerwolf.com/contact/).

Thank you,

Luna & Sol

Last update: _September 01, 2018_
